oneskyapp.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy - OneSky

Last Updated: May 25, 2018

## Introduction

OneSky values your privacy and is committed to safeguard your privacy online.This “Privacy Policy” explains how OneSky Inc. Limited (collectively “OneSky“, or “We“, or “Us“, or “Our“) collects, uses and shares your personal information in connection with your use of www.oneskyapp.com (the “Website“) and Our services, and explains your choices for how we handle your personal information. For convenience, the Website and Our services are collectively referred to as the “Services.” This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information of users of the Website or Services.

## Scope of this Policy

In this Policy, Personal Information means information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. An identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his/her physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. Subscribers to Our Services are solely responsible for establishing policies for and ensuring compliance with all applicable laws and regulations, as well as any and all privacy policies, agreements or other obligations, relating to the collection of personal information in connection with the use of Our Services by individuals with whom the user who registers to us Our Services (“Subscriber”) interact. If you are an individual who interacts with Our Subscribers using Our Services, then you will be directed to contact Our Subscribers for assistance with any requests or questions relating to your personal information. We collect information under the direction of Our Subscribers, and have no direct relationship with individuals whose personal information we process in connection with the use of Our Services. If you are an individual who interacts with a Subscriber using Our Services (such as a customer of a Subscriber) and would no longer like to be contacted by the Subscriber that use Our Services, please contact the Subscriber that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide Our Services. Transfers to subsequent third parties for these purposes are governed by the Service Agreements with Our Subscribers.

## Information That We Collect

We collect personal information about you in the following ways:

### 1\. Information that you provide to us

Personal information that you may provide through the Services or otherwise communicate with us includes:

  * Identity information, such as your first name, last name, username or similar identifier, title;
  * Contact information, such as your postal address, email address and telephone number;
  * Profile information, such as your username and password, feedback and survey responses;
  * Feedback and correspondence, such as information you provide in your responses to surveys, when you participate in market research activities, report a problem with Service, receive customer support or otherwise correspond with us;
  * Financial information, such as your credit card or other payment card details;
  * Transaction information, such details about purchases you make through the Service and billing details;
  * Usage information, such as information about how you use the Service and interact with us;
  * Marketing information, such your preferences for receiving marketing communications and details about how you engage with them;

We refer to any information described above as “Account Information” for the purposes of this Policy. By voluntarily providing Us with Account Information, you represent that you are the owner of such personal data or are otherwise authorized to provide it to us.

### 2\. Information automatically collected

Our servers may automatically record certain information about how you use the Website (we refer to this information as “Log Data“), including clients of Our services (“Clients”), Website visitors and Subscribers. Log Data may include information such as a user’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, device and browser type, operating system, the pages or features of Our Website to which a user browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, the frequency with which the Website is used by a user, search terms, the links on Our Website that a user clicked on or used, and other statistics. We use this information to administer the Services and We analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding its features and functionality and tailoring it to Our users’ needs and preferences.

We partner with third-party service providers to use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users’ movements around the Website, and to gather demographic information about Our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

### 3\. Information that We get from other sources

**Social Media Widgets:** The Website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on Our Website. These features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on the Website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the companies that provide them.

**Single Sign-On:** You can log into certain Services using sign-in services such as GitHub. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you with the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and pre-populate Our sign up form.

## How We use the Information Collected

### General Uses

If you have OneSky account, We use the information we collect about you (including personal information, to the extent applicable) for a variety of purposes, including to

(a) operate, maintain, administer and improve the Services; (b) process payments you make through the Services, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices; (c) send transactional messages, including responses to your comments, questions, and requests; provide customer service and support; and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages; (e) respond to your Service-related requests, questions and feedback; (f) monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Websites and Services and for marketing or advertising purposes; (i) personalize the Websites and Services, including by providing features or advertisements that match your interests and preferences; and (j) for other purposes for which we obtain your consent.

### To comply with law

We use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws, lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities.

### With your consent

We may use or share your personal information with your consent, such as when you consent to let us post your testimonials or endorsements on the Website, you instruct Us to take a specific action with respect to your personal information or you opt into third party marketing communications.

## How We share the Information Collected

We do not share or sell the personal information that you provide us with other organizations without your express consent, except as described in this Privacy Policy. We disclose personal information to third parties under the following circumstances:

### Third-Party Service Providers:

We share information, including personal information, with Our third-party service providers that we use to provide hosting for and maintenance of Our Websites, application development, backup, storage, payment processing, analytics and other services for us. These third-party service providers may have access to or process your personal information for the purpose of providing these services for us. We do not permit Our third-party service providers to use the personal information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us. (List of data sub-processor)

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Our Rights:

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may disclose personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise Our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Our service agreement, or as otherwise required by law.

### Testimonials:

From time to time, we may post testimonials on the Website that may contain personal information. We obtain your consent to post your name along with your testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@oneskyapp.com.

### Community Forums:

Our Website may offer publicly accessible blogs, community forums, comments sections, discussion forums, or other interactive features (“Interactive Areas”). You should be aware that any information that you post in an Interactive Area might be read, collected, and used by others who access it. To request removal of your personal information from an Interactive Area, contact us at support@oneskyapp.com. In some cases, We may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case We will let you know if We are unable to do so and why.

## Your Rights

You may be entitled to:

  * opt out from processing of your personal Information for direct marketing purposes;
  * request information regarding the processing of your personal Information, including to be provided with a copy of your personal data;
  * request the correction and/or deletion of your personal Information, or object to the processing of your personal Information;
  * request receipt or transmission to another organization, in a machine-readable form, of the personal Information that you have provided to us; and
  * complain to your local data protection authority, or to a court of law, if your data protection rights are violated.

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at support@oneskyapp.com. Subscribers to Our Services may update or change their Account Information by editing their profile or organization record by logging into their Account or by contacting support@oneskyapp.com for more detailed instructions. To make a request to have personal information maintained by us returned to you or removed, please email support@oneskyapp.com. Requests to access, change, or remove your information will be handled within 30 days. An individual who seeks access to, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccuracies in personal information stored or processed by us on behalf of a Subscriber should direct his/her query to the Subscriber (the data controller). Upon receipt of a request from one of Our Subscribers for us to remove the data, we will respond to their request within thirty (30) days. We will retain personal information that we store and process on behalf of Our Subscribers for as long as needed to provide the Services to Our Subscribers. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with Our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce Our agreements.

If you are a Subscriber or otherwise provide us with personal information in connection with your use of Our Website or Services, we will delete this information upon your request, provided that, notwithstanding such request, this information may be retained for as long as you maintain an account for Our Services, or as needed to provide you with Our Services, comply with Our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce Our agreements.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at support@oneskyapp.com.

## Children’s Personal Information

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through Our Website or Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide personal information through the Website or Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to Us through the Website or Services, please contact Us at support@oneskyapp.com, and We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information.

## Business Transactions

We may assign or transfer this Policy, as well as your account and related information and data, including any personal information, to any person or entity that acquires all or substantially all of Our business, stock or assets, or with whom we merge.

## Other Websites and Services

Our Website may contain links to other websites and the information practices and the content of such other websites are governed by the privacy statements of such other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any such other websites to understand their information practices.

## COOKIES

What is a Cookie? A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Some of the cookies will only be used if you use certain features or select certain preferences, and some cookies will always be used. Web beacons, tags and scripts may be used in the Website or in emails to help us to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by our service/analytics providers on an individual and aggregated basis. OneSky and Our marketing partners, affiliates, and analytics or service providers use cookies and other technologies to ensure everyone who uses the Website has the best possible experience.

When you visit the Websites, We may place a number of cookies in your browser. For example, we use cookies on the Website to understand visitor and user preferences, improve their experience, and track and analyze usage, navigational and other statistical information. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you disable cookies, you may still visit the Website, but your ability to use some features or areas of the Websites may be limited.

If you want to learn more about cookies, or how to control, disable or delete them, please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance. In addition, certain third party advertising networks, including Google, permit users to opt out of or customize preferences associated with your internet browsing. To learn more about this feature from Google, click here.

## User Generated Content

We may make available on Our Website, or link to, features that allow you to share information online (e.g., community forums, on message boards, in chat areas, in file uploads, through events, etc.). Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. We have no control over, and take no responsibility for, the use, storage or dissemination of such publicly-disclosed personal information. By posting personal information online in public forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

## Changes To This Policy

If there are any material changes to this Policy, you will be notified by Our posting of a prominent notice on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on Our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Website or the Services constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to this Policy. Your only remedy, if you do not accept the terms of this Policy, is to discontinue use of the Websites and the Services.

## Contact Us

If you have questions regarding this Policy or about OneSky privacy practices, please contact us by email at [support@oneskyapp.com](mailto:support@oneskyapp.com).
